A Guide to the Militia Commission Papers, 1777-1858
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Militia Commissions, 1777-1858., Extent: 66.71 cu. ft. (169 boxes). (Box 3-171)
  - Subseries A. Counties, 1777-1858.
    - Pendleton County, 1840. (Box 121, Folder 47)
    - Pendleton County, 1841. (Box 121, Folder 48)
    - Pendleton County, 1842. (Box 121, Folder 49)
    - Pendleton County, 1843. (Box 121, Folder 50)
    - Pendleton County, 1844. (Box 121, Folder 51)
    - Pendleton County, 1845. (Box 121, Folder 52)
    - Pendleton County, 1846. (Box 121, Folder 53)
    - Pendleton County, 1847. (Box 121, Folder 54)
    - Pendleton County, 1848. (Box 121, Folder 55)
    - Pendleton County, 1849. (Box 121, Folder 56)
    - Pendleton County, 1850. (Box 121, Folder 57)
    - Pendleton County, 1851. (Box 121, Folder 58)
    - Pendleton County, 1852. (Box 121, Folder 59)
    - Pendleton County, 1853. (Box 121, Folder 60)
    - Pendleton County, undated. (Box 121, Folder 61)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1784. (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1785. (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1787. (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1788. (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1789. (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1790. (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1791. (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1793. (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1794. (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1795. (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1796. (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1797. (Box 122, Folder 12)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1798. (Box 122, Folder 13)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1799. (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1800. (Box 122, Folder 15)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1801. (Box 122, Folder 16)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1802. (Box 122, Folder 17)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1803. (Box 122, Folder 18)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1804. (Box 122, Folder 19)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1805. (Box 122, Folder 20)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1806. (Box 122, Folder 21)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1807. (Box 122, Folder 22)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1808. (Box 122, Folder 23)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1809. (Box 122, Folder 24)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1810. (Box 122, Folder 25)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1811. (Box 122, Folder 26)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1812. (Box 122, Folder 27)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1813. (Box 122, Folder 28)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1814. (Box 122, Folder 29)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1815. (Box 122, Folder 30)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1816. (Box 122, Folder 31)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1817. (Box 122, Folder 32)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1818. (Box 122, Folder 33)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1819. (Box 122, Folder 34)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1820. (Box 122, Folder 35)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1821. (Box 122, Folder 36)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1822. (Box 122, Folder 37)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1823. (Box 122, Folder 38)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1824. (Box 122, Folder 39)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1825. (Box 122, Folder 40)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1826. (Box 122, Folder 41)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1827. (Box 122, Folder 42)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1828. (Box 122, Folder 43)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1829. (Box 122, Folder 44)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1830. (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1831. (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1832. (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1833. (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1834. (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1835. (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1836. (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1837. (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1838. (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1839. (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1840. (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1841. (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1842. (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1843. (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1844. (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1845. (Box 123, Folder 16)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1846. (Box 123, Folder 17)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1847. (Box 123, Folder 18)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1848. (Box 123, Folder 19)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1849. (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1850. (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1851. (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1852. (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1853. (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1854. (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1855. (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1856. (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Pittsylvania County, undated. (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Pocahontas County, 1822. (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Pocahontas County, 1823. (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Pocahontas County, 1824. (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - Pocahontas County, 1825. (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Pocahontas County, 1826. (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Pocahontas County, 1827. (Box 124, Folder 15)
    - Pocahontas County, 1828. (Box 124, Folder 16)
    - Pocahontas County, 1829. (Box 124, Folder 17)
    - Pocahontas County, 1830. (Box 124, Folder 18)
    - Pocahontas County, 1831. (Box 124, Folder 19)
    - Pocahontas County, 1832. (Box 124, Folder 20)
    - Pocahontas County, 1833. (Box 124, Folder 21)
    - Pocahontas County, 1834. (Box 124, Folder 22)
    - Pocahontas County, 1835. (Box 124, Folder 23)
    - Pocahontas County, 1836. (Box 124, Folder 24)
    - Pocahontas County, 1837. (Box 124, Folder 25)
    - Pocahontas County, 1838. (Box 124, Folder 26)
    - Pocahontas County, 1839. (Box 124, Folder 27)
    - Pocahontas County, 1840. (Box 124, Folder 28)
    - Pocahontas County, 1841. (Box 124, Folder 29)
    - Pocahontas County, 1842. (Box 124, Folder 30)
    - Pocahontas County, 1843. (Box 124, Folder 31)
    - Pocahontas County, 1844. (Box 124, Folder 32)
    - Pocahontas County, 1845. (Box 124, Folder 33)
    - Pocahontas County, 1846. (Box 124, Folder 34)
    - Pocahontas County, 1847. (Box 124, Folder 35)
    - Pocahontas County, 1848. (Box 124, Folder 36)
    - Pocahontas County, 1849. (Box 124, Folder 37)
    - Pocahontas County, 1850. (Box 124, Folder 38)
    - Pocahontas County, 1851. (Box 124, Folder 39)
    - Pocahontas County, 1852. (Box 124, Folder 40)
    - Pocahontas County, 1853. (Box 124, Folder 41)
    - Pocahontas County, 1856. (Box 124, Folder 42)
    - Pocahontas County, undated. (Box 124, Folder 43)
    - Powhatan County, 1781. (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Powhatan County, 1785. (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Powhatan County, 1786. (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Powhatan County, 1787. (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Powhatan County, 1788. (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Powhatan County, 1789. (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Powhatan County, 1790. (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Powhatan County, 1793. (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Powhatan County, 1794. (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Powhatan County, 1795. (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Powhatan County, 1796. (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Powhatan County, 1797. (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Powhatan County, 1798. (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Powhatan County, 1799. (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - Powhatan County, 1800. (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - Powhatan County, 1801. (Box 125, Folder 16)
    - Powhatan County, 1802. (Box 125, Folder 17)
    - Powhatan County, 1803. (Box 125, Folder 18)
    - Powhatan County, 1804. (Box 125, Folder 19)
    - Powhatan County, 1805. (Box 125, Folder 20)
    - Powhatan County, 1806. (Box 125, Folder 21)
    - Powhatan County, 1807. (Box 125, Folder 22)
    - Powhatan County, 1808. (Box 125, Folder 23)
    - Powhatan County, 1809. (Box 125, Folder 24)
    - Powhatan County, 1810. (Box 125, Folder 25)
    - Powhatan County, 1811. (Box 125, Folder 26)
    - Powhatan County, 1812. (Box 125, Folder 27)
    - Powhatan County, 1813. (Box 125, Folder 28)
    - Powhatan County, 1814. (Box 125, Folder 29)
    - Powhatan County, 1815. (Box 125, Folder 30)
    - Powhatan County, 1816. (Box 125, Folder 31)
    - Powhatan County, 1817. (Box 125, Folder 32)
    - Powhatan County, 1818. (Box 125, Folder 33)
    - Powhatan County, 1819. (Box 125, Folder 34)
    - Powhatan County, 1820. (Box 125, Folder 35)
    - Powhatan County, 1821. (Box 125, Folder 36)
    - Powhatan County, 1822. (Box 125, Folder 37)
    - Powhatan County, 1823. (Box 125, Folder 38)
    - Powhatan County, 1824. (Box 125, Folder 39)
    - Powhatan County, 1825. (Box 125, Folder 40)
    - Powhatan County, 1826. (Box 125, Folder 41)
    - Powhatan County, 1827. (Box 125, Folder 42)
    - Powhatan County, 1828. (Box 125, Folder 43)
    - Powhatan County, 1830. (Box 125, Folder 44)
    - Powhatan County, 1831. (Box 125, Folder 45)
    - Powhatan County, 1832. (Box 125, Folder 46)
    - Powhatan County, 1833. (Box 125, Folder 47)
    - Powhatan County, 1834. (Box 125, Folder 48)
    - Powhatan County, 1835. (Box 125, Folder 49)
    - Powhatan County, 1836. (Box 125, Folder 50)
    - Powhatan County, 1837. (Box 125, Folder 51)
    - Powhatan County, 1838. (Box 125, Folder 52)
    - Powhatan County, 1839. (Box 125, Folder 53)
    - Powhatan County, 1840. (Box 125, Folder 54)
    - Powhatan County, 1841. (Box 125, Folder 55)
    - Powhatan County, 1842. (Box 125, Folder 56)
    - Powhatan County, 1843. (Box 125, Folder 57)
    - Powhatan County, 1844. (Box 125, Folder 58)
    - Powhatan County, 1845. (Box 125, Folder 59)
    - Powhatan County, 1846. (Box 125, Folder 60)
    - Powhatan County, 1847. (Box 125, Folder 61)
    - Powhatan County, 1848. (Box 125, Folder 62)
    - Powhatan County, 1849. (Box 125, Folder 63)
    - Powhatan County, 1850. (Box 125, Folder 64)
    - Powhatan County, 1851. (Box 125, Folder 65)
    - Powhatan County, 1852. (Box 125, Folder 66)
    - Powhatan County, 1853. (Box 125, Folder 67)
    - Powhatan County, 1856. (Box 125, Folder 68)
    - Powhatan County, undated. (Box 125, Folder 69)
    - Preston County, 1815. (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Preston County, 1818. (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Preston County, 1819. (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Preston County, 1820. (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Preston County, 1821. (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Preston County, 1822. (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Preston County, 1824. (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Preston County, 1825. (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Preston County, 1826. (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Preston County, 1827. (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Preston County, 1829. (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - Preston County, 1830. (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - Preston County, 1833. (Box 126, Folder 13)
    - Preston County, 1834. (Box 126, Folder 14)
    - Preston County, 1835. (Box 126, Folder 15)
    - Preston County, 1836. (Box 126, Folder 16)
    - Preston County, 1837. (Box 126, Folder 17)
    - Preston County, 1838. (Box 126, Folder 18)
    - Preston County, 1839. (Box 126, Folder 19)
    - Preston County, 1840. (Box 126, Folder 20)
    - Preston County, 1841. (Box 126, Folder 21)
    - Preston County, 1842. (Box 126, Folder 22)
    - Preston County, 1843. (Box 126, Folder 23)
    - Preston County, 1844. (Box 126, Folder 24)
    - Preston County, 1845. (Box 126, Folder 25)
    - Preston County, 1846. (Box 126, Folder 26)
    - Preston County, 1847. (Box 126, Folder 27)
    - Preston County, 1848. (Box 126, Folder 28)
    - Preston County, 1849. (Box 126, Folder 29)
    - Preston County, 1850. (Box 126, Folder 30)
    - Preston County, 1851. (Box 126, Folder 31)
    - Preston County, 1852. (Box 126, Folder 32)
    - Preston County, 1853. (Box 126, Folder 33)
    - Preston County, undated. (Box 126, Folder 34)
    - Prince Edward County, 1784. (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Prince Edward County, 1785. (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Prince Edward County, 1786. (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Prince Edward County, 1787. (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Prince Edward County, 1788. (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Prince Edward County, 1789. (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Prince Edward County, 1793. (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Prince Edward County, 1794. (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Prince Edward County, 1795. (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Prince Edward County, 1796. (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Prince Edward County, 1797. (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - Prince Edward County, 1798. (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - Prince Edward County, 1799. (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - Prince Edward County, 1800. (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - Prince Edward County, 1801. (Box 127, Folder 15)
    - Prince Edward County, 1802. (Box 127, Folder 16)
    - Prince Edward County, 1803. (Box 127, Folder 17)
    - Prince Edward County, 1804. (Box 127, Folder 18)
    - Prince Edward County, 1805. (Box 127, Folder 19)
    - Prince Edward County, 1806. (Box 127, Folder 20)
    - Prince Edward County, 1807. (Box 127, Folder 21)
    - Prince Edward County, 1808. (Box 127, Folder 22)
    - Prince Edward County, 1809. (Box 127, Folder 23)
    - Prince Edward County, 1810. (Box 127, Folder 24)
    - Prince Edward County, 1811. (Box 127, Folder 25)
    - Prince Edward County, 1812. (Box 127, Folder 26)
    - Prince Edward County, 1813. (Box 127, Folder 27)
    - Prince Edward County, 1814. (Box 127, Folder 28)
    - Prince Edward County, 1815. (Box 127, Folder 29)
    - Prince Edward County, 1816. (Box 127, Folder 30)
    - Prince Edward County, 1817. (Box 127, Folder 31)
    - Prince Edward County, 1818. (Box 127, Folder 32)
    - Prince Edward County, 1819. (Box 127, Folder 33)
    - Prince Edward County, 1820. (Box 127, Folder 34)
    - Prince Edward County, 1821. (Box 127, Folder 35)
    - Prince Edward County, 1822. (Box 127, Folder 36)
    - Prince Edward County, 1823. (Box 127, Folder 37)
    - Prince Edward County, 1824. (Box 127, Folder 38)
    - Prince Edward County, 1826. (Box 127, Folder 39)
    - Prince Edward County, 1827. (Box 127, Folder 40)
    - Prince Edward County, 1828. (Box 127, Folder 41)
    - Prince Edward County, 1829. (Box 127, Folder 42)
    - Prince Edward County, 1830. (Box 127, Folder 43)
    - Prince Edward County, 1831. (Box 127, Folder 44)
    - Prince Edward County, 1832. (Box 127, Folder 45)
    - Prince Edward County, 1833. (Box 127, Folder 46)
    - Prince Edward County, 1834. (Box 127, Folder 47)
    - Prince Edward County, 1835. (Box 127, Folder 48)
    - Prince Edward County, 1836. (Box 127, Folder 49)
    - Prince Edward County, 1837. (Box 127, Folder 50)
    - Prince Edward County, 1838. (Box 127, Folder 51)
    - Prince Edward County, 1839. (Box 127, Folder 52)
    - Prince Edward County, 1840. (Box 127, Folder 53)
    - Prince Edward County, 1841. (Box 127, Folder 54)
    - Prince Edward County, 1842. (Box 127, Folder 55)
    - Prince Edward County, 1843. (Box 127, Folder 56)
    - Prince Edward County, 1844. (Box 127, Folder 57)
    - Prince Edward County, 1845. (Box 127, Folder 58)
    - Prince Edward County, 1846. (Box 127, Folder 59)
    - Prince Edward County, 1848. (Box 127, Folder 60)
    - Prince Edward County, 1849. (Box 127, Folder 61)
    - Prince Edward County, 1850. (Box 127, Folder 62)
    - Prince Edward County, 1851. (Box 127, Folder 63)
    - Prince Edward County, 1852. (Box 127, Folder 64)
    - Prince Edward County, 1853. (Box 127, Folder 65)
    - Prince Edward County, 1854. (Box 127, Folder 66)
    - Prince Edward County, 1855. (Box 127, Folder 67)
    - Prince Edward County, 1856. (Box 127, Folder 68)
    - Prince Edward County, undated. (Box 127, Folder 69)
    - Prince George County, 1785. (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Prince George County, 1786. (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Prince George County, 1787. (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Prince George County, 1788. (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Prince George County, 1789. (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Prince George County, 1790. (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Prince George County, 1791. (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Prince George County, 1793. (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Prince George County, 1794. (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Prince George County, 1795. (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Prince George County, 1796. (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - Prince George County, 1797. (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - Prince George County, 1798. (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - Prince George County, 1799. (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - Prince George County, 1800. (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - Prince George County, 1801. (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - Prince George County, 1802. (Box 128, Folder 17)
    - Prince George County, 1803. (Box 128, Folder 18)
    - Prince George County, 1804. (Box 128, Folder 19)
    - Prince George County, 1805. (Box 128, Folder 20)
    - Prince George County, 1806. (Box 128, Folder 21)
    - Prince George County, 1807. (Box 128, Folder 22)
    - Prince George County, 1808. (Box 128, Folder 23)
    - Prince George County, 1809. (Box 128, Folder 24)
    - Prince George County, 1811. (Box 128, Folder 25)
    - Prince George County, 1812. (Box 128, Folder 26)
    - Prince George County, 1813. (Box 128, Folder 27)
    - Prince George County, 1814. (Box 128, Folder 28)
    - Prince George County, 1815. (Box 128, Folder 29)
    - Prince George County, 1816. (Box 128, Folder 30)
    - Prince George County, 1817. (Box 128, Folder 31)
    - Prince George County, 1818. (Box 128, Folder 32)
    - Prince George County, 1819. (Box 128, Folder 33)
    - Prince George County, 1820. (Box 128, Folder 34)
    - Prince George County, 1821. (Box 128, Folder 35)
    - Prince George County, 1822. (Box 128, Folder 36)
    - Prince George County, 1823. (Box 128, Folder 37)
    - Prince George County, 1824. (Box 128, Folder 38)
    - Prince George County, 1825. (Box 128, Folder 39)
    - Prince George County, 1826. (Box 128, Folder 40)
    - Prince George County, 1827. (Box 128, Folder 41)
    - Prince George County, 1828. (Box 128, Folder 42)
    - Prince George County, 1829. (Box 128, Folder 43)
    - Prince George County, 1830. (Box 128, Folder 44)
    - Prince George County, 1831. (Box 128, Folder 45)
    - Prince George County, 1832. (Box 128, Folder 46)
    - Prince George County, 1833. (Box 128, Folder 47)
    - Prince George County, 1834. (Box 128, Folder 48)
    - Prince George County, 1835. (Box 128, Folder 49)
    - Prince George County, 1836. (Box 128, Folder 50)
    - Prince George County, 1837. (Box 128, Folder 51)
    - Prince George County, 1838. (Box 128, Folder 52)
    - Prince George County, 1839. (Box 128, Folder 53)
    - Prince George County, 1840. (Box 128, Folder 54)
    - Prince George County, 1841. (Box 128, Folder 55)
    - Prince George County, 1842. (Box 128, Folder 56)
    - Prince George County, 1843. (Box 128, Folder 57)
    - Prince George County, 1844. (Box 128, Folder 58)
    - Prince George County, 1845. (Box 128, Folder 59)
    - Prince George County, 1846. (Box 128, Folder 60)
    - Prince George County, 1847. (Box 128, Folder 61)
    - Prince George County, 1848. (Box 128, Folder 62)
    - Prince George County, 1849. (Box 128, Folder 63)
    - Prince George County, 1850. (Box 128, Folder 64)
    - Prince George County, 1851. (Box 128, Folder 65)
    - Prince George County, 1853. (Box 128, Folder 66)
    - Prince George County, 1856. (Box 128, Folder 67)
    - Prince George County, undated. (Box 128, Folder 68)
    - Prince William County, 1783. (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Prince William County, 1785. (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Prince William County, 1787. (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Prince William County, 1788. (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Prince William County, 1793. (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Prince William County, 1794. (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Prince William County, 1795. (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Prince William County, 1796. (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Prince William County, 1797. (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Prince William County, 1798. (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Prince William County, 1799. (Box 129, Folder 11)
    - Prince William County, 1800. (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Prince William County, 1801. (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - Prince William County, 1803. (Box 129, Folder 14)
    - Prince William County, 1804. (Box 129, Folder 15)
    - Prince William County, 1805. (Box 129, Folder 16)
    - Prince William County, 1806. (Box 129, Folder 17)
    - Prince William County, 1807. (Box 129, Folder 18)
    - Prince William County, 1808. (Box 129, Folder 19)
    - Prince William County, 1809. (Box 129, Folder 20)
    - Prince William County, 1810. (Box 129, Folder 21)
    - Prince William County, 1811. (Box 129, Folder 22)
    - Prince William County, 1812. (Box 129, Folder 23)
    - Prince William County, 1813. (Box 129, Folder 24)
    - Prince William County, 1814. (Box 129, Folder 25)
    - Prince William County, 1816. (Box 129, Folder 26)
    - Prince William County, 1817. (Box 129, Folder 27)
    - Prince William County, 1818. (Box 129, Folder 28)
    - Prince William County, 1819. (Box 129, Folder 29)
    - Prince William County, 1820. (Box 129, Folder 30)
    - Prince William County, 1821. (Box 129, Folder 31)
    - Prince William County, 1822. (Box 129, Folder 32)
    - Prince William County, 1823. (Box 129, Folder 33)
    - Prince William County, 1824. (Box 129, Folder 34)
    - Prince William County, 1825. (Box 129, Folder 35)
    - Prince William County, 1826. (Box 129, Folder 36)
    - Prince William County, 1827. (Box 129, Folder 37)
    - Prince William County, 1828. (Box 129, Folder 38)
    - Prince William County, 1829. (Box 129, Folder 39)
    - Prince William County, 1830. (Box 129, Folder 40)
    - Prince William County, 1831. (Box 129, Folder 41)
    - Prince William County, 1832. (Box 129, Folder 42)
    - Prince William County, 1833. (Box 129, Folder 43)
    - Prince William County, 1834. (Box 129, Folder 44)
    - Prince William County, 1835. (Box 129, Folder 45)
    - Prince William County, 1836. (Box 129, Folder 46)
    - Prince William County, 1837. (Box 129, Folder 47)
    - Prince William County, 1838. (Box 129, Folder 48)
    - Prince William County, 1839. (Box 129, Folder 49)
    - Prince William County, 1840. (Box 129, Folder 50)
    - Prince William County, 1841. (Box 129, Folder 51)
    - Prince William County, 1842. (Box 129, Folder 52)
    - Prince William County, 1843. (Box 129, Folder 53)
    - Prince William County, 1844. (Box 129, Folder 54)
    - Prince William County, 1845. (Box 129, Folder 55)
    - Prince William County, 1846. (Box 129, Folder 56)
    - Prince William County, 1847. (Box 129, Folder 57)
    - Prince William County, 1848. (Box 129, Folder 58)
    - Prince William County, 1849. (Box 129, Folder 59)
    - Prince William County, 1850. (Box 129, Folder 60)
    - Prince William County, 1851. (Box 129, Folder 61)
    - Prince William County, 1852. (Box 129, Folder 62)
    - Prince William County, 1853. (Box 129, Folder 63)
    - Prince William County, 1855. (Box 129, Folder 64)
    - Prince William County, undated. (Box 129, Folder 65)
    - Princess Anne County, 1783. (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Princess Anne County, 1784. (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Princess Anne County, 1785. (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Princess Anne County, 1787. (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Princess Anne County, 1788. (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Princess Anne County, 1789. (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Princess Anne County, 1790. (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Princess Anne County, 1792. (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Princess Anne County, 1793. (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Princess Anne County, 1794. (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Princess Anne County, 1796. (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - Princess Anne County, 1797. (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - Princess Anne County, 1798. (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - Princess Anne County, 1799. (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Princess Anne County, 1801. (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - Princess Anne County, 1803. (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - Princess Anne County, 1806. (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - Princess Anne County, 1807. (Box 130, Folder 18)
    - Princess Anne County, 1808. (Box 130, Folder 19)
    - Princess Anne County, 1809. (Box 130, Folder 20)